you don't receive any grace from the King or
tú no recibes ninguna gracia del Rey ni
anything if you haven't paid you have to pay it
nada si no has pagado tiene que pagarlo
whole indexation [ __ ] that is to say When
indización entera es decir Cuando
Yuji went to jail I had to
yuji entró en la cárcel yo tuve que
pay a million and a half bats
pagar un millón y medio de bats
directly because if not they would take away our
directamente porque si no nos quitaban
house we have to compensate for the damage It's always
la casa hay que resarcir el daño Siempre
that if not what's the point of that
es que si no que sentido tiene ese
pardon he has to pay whatever they
perdón tiene que pagar lo que le
condemn him for here it is paid you have to pay it and you have no choice
condenen aquí se paga hay que pagarlo y
and if you don't pay it you don't
no te queda otra y si no lo pagas no
start counting pardons then of
empiezas a contar perdones entonces
course I don't know why they are spending
claro Yo no sé por qué se están gastando
all this money instead of making a pact with
todo este dinero en vez de pactar con
Edwin's lawyers and saying Hey
los abogados de Edwin y decir Oye lo
we admit everything but let's tone it down a bit
admitimos todo pero bajarnos un poco el
because we are screwed they are
tema porque estamos jodidos están
doing everything backwards and it's because of
haciéndolo todo al revés y es por la
[ __ ] arrogance and in the end what is
prepotencia y al final qué va a
Mr. Sancho going to do he is going to go to
hacer el señor Sancho se va a poner en
Spain to ask for a collection from all the
España a pedir una colecta a todos los
actors and all the journalists Hey
actores y a todos los periodistas Oye
Give me money that I need
Darme dinero que me hace falta